http://www.dmainc.com/about/privacy-policy

Website Privacy Policy
DMA is a tax consulting firm based in North America (the United States and Canada) that assists companies with solving their corporate indirect tax challenges in seven key areas: property tax, sales/use and commodity tax, state income and franchise tax, tax technology, value added tax, crown royalties and unclaimed property. DMA recognizes the importance of your privacy. This policy explains how we use and disclose personal information that we collect about you. By submitting personal information to us, you agree to the use of such information, including any disclosures, processing, and transfers of your information to third parties by DMA, in accordance with this policy. If you do not agree, do not submit any personal information to us.
Scope of Policy
This policy applies to personal information that we collect (i) directly from you (for example, if you engage us to provide services, visit our website, sign-up to receive our marketing communications, send us an email, provide us a business card, attend an event sponsored by us, or submit a job application), (ii) in the course of providing our services to you or a third party, such as your employer, or (iii) from other publicly available sources, such as LinkedIn.
Our website may include links to third party websites. These third party websites have their own privacy policies and terms of use and are not controlled by this policy or the terms of our website’s terms of use. You should carefully review any terms, conditions and policies of such third party websites before visiting them or supplying them with any personal information. We are not responsible for the privacy or security of any information you provide to a third party website that is linked from our website and the inclusion of such a link does not constitute any type of endorsement of the linked site by us. We are not responsible for any loss or damage you may sustain resulting from your use of any third party website or any information you share with a third party website.
Personal Information
In order to use our website, you are not required to provide us with your personal information.  However, we may be unable to provide you with information you request if you do not provide us with some or all of the personal information requested via our website. You may voluntarily provide us with personal information, such as your name, email address, telephone number, company name and other business contact information when registering for events, seminars or webinars, when making selections on our subscription center as to the types of information you would like to receive, or when applying for employment.
In connection with providing our services to our clients, we enter into contracts that describe the scope of services for which information is collected and used. A client that provides us with personal information of any individual (including its employees) is responsible for obtaining from such persons any consents required to provide such information to us.
We may store your name, email address, and other contact information such as company, title and industry in a customer relationship management tool and use it to manage our relationship with you or your company/employer.
Automatic Collection
We automatically collect information regarding visitors’ use of our website without any personal or identifying information. This information includes: domain name from which a user accesses the Internet, the date and time and duration user was connected to the website, the Internet address of the website from which a user linked directly to this website, the type of browser used to access this website and the search engine and keywords used when searching for this website. This information is in aggregate to measure website performance.
Like many other websites, our website uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that are downloaded to the browser of a computer, tablet or smartphone used to visit a website. A cookie will identify your browser, help you log in and improve the navigation of a website. We use cookies to help us improve the performance of our website. Cookies allow us to review the number of visitors to our website and understand a visitor’s usage patterns; track key performance indicators such as pages visited, frequency of visits, downloads and other statistical information; know whether a visitor views the mobile or desktop version of our website; recognize visitors if they return to our website; store information about visitors’ past visits; and remember visitors’ preferences.
You may be able to disallow cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. If you choose not to accept cookies, you may be unable to access certain parts or pages of our website.
We or our digital media service providers also use Web beacons; a small transparent image also referred to as a tracking pixel to help us better understand the effectiveness of our content and advertisement, the interests of our visitors, and to improve visitor experience on the website. These beacons allow us to determine which visitors have come to the website after viewing an advertisement we have served on third party websites. We also work with such third parties to collect data so that we can determine the effectiveness of our ads and serve ads targeted to your interests. The use of Web beacons does not provide us with any personal information and we do not use this technology to access your personal information. It is used only to compile aggregated data about visitors to the website.
Web beacons do not place information on your device, but may work in conjunction with cookies to monitor activity. You have the option to render some Web beacons unusable by rejecting their associated cookies. The Web beacon may still record an anonymous visit from your IP address, but cookie information will not be recorded.
In some of our newsletters and other email communications, we may monitor recipient actions such as email open rates through embedded links within the messages. If you do not wish us to confirm whether you have opened, clicked or forwarded our email marketing communications, you will need to unsubscribe as it is not possible for us to send these emails without tracking enabled. Registered subscribers can update their subscription preferences at any time by following the instructions in the individual email communications you receive from us.
Use, Disclosures and Transfers
We use the personal information we collect in the course of conducting our business to, among other things:
Fulfill your requests or any other purpose for which you provided information to us.
Provide invitations to or register you for events, seminars or webinars.
Provide newsletters and marketing information to you.
Provide continuing professional education (CPE) to you, which may include sharing your personal and CPE information with the appropriate professional organizations so that you receive CPE credit.
Respond to your inquiries, process your requests, investigate and address your concerns, and monitor and improve our responses.
Help maintain the safety, security and integrity of our website, products, services and other technical assets and business.
Improve or modify our website.
Update and maintain client, subscription or email lists and for other internal purposes.
Deliver our products and perform our services.
Provide communications about our products and services.
Respond to requests for information or requests for proposals, or provide information about products or services you request.
Respond to lawful requests for information through court orders, subpoenas, warrants and other types of legal process or obligations.
Establish, exercise or defend legal claims.
Evaluate job applications and compile applicant data for reporting purposes.
Investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or violations of our website terms of use or this policy.
We will not disclose an individual’s personal information to third parties, except as set forth in this policy, when we have permission to make the disclosure, or as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the information was provided to us. We may also use or disclose personal information as we believe to be necessary or appropriate (i) under applicable law; (ii) to comply with legal process or professional standards; (iii) to protect our rights or property and/or those of our affiliates or clients; (iv) in a merger, acquisition or asset sale; or (v) to our affiliates. We will not share or sell your personal information to third parties for their own marketing purposes, except we may share invitee/attendee contact information with event co-sponsors.
We may use third party service providers (for example, professional advisors, insurers, benefit providers, contractors or other third party service providers who we engage to support our internal operations or assist with the services we provide) to provide administrative, marketing, or operational services to us, and depending on the services they may have access to personal information in connection with their services.
We may share your personal information and non-personal information in connection with or during negotiations of any proposed or actual financing of our business, or merger, purchase, sale, joint venture, or any other type of acquisition or business combination of all or any portion of our assets, or transfer of all or a portion of our business to another company, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding.
Data Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We seek to use reasonable and appropriate safeguards to protect your information, which includes physical, technical and administrative measures. However, no method of transferring data over the internet or storing electronic data is entirely secure, so while we strive to use reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee security against all threats.
Marketing Opt Out
If you would like to opt out of receiving promotional or marketing email from us, you may use the “unsubscribe” or “opt out” mechanism included in each marketing email or you may opt out by visiting our subscription center at https://www.dmainc.com/subscribe. Please be aware that your option to not receive promotional and marketing email from us does not preclude us from corresponding with you by email or otherwise regarding your existing relationship with us.
Canadian Residents
Any personal information a resident of Canada provides to us is protected under the federal Personal Information Protection and Electronic Document Act or British Columbia’s or Alberta’s Personal Information Protection Act. If there is a discrepancy between any of the provisions of this policy and the requirements of the aforementioned laws involving an individual who is a resident of Canada, the applicable law shall govern our obligations and responses.
Any information you provide via our website and any technical information from the browser of your computer, tablet or mobile device will be transferred out of Canada and into the United States. If you do not want any personal information to be transferred to the United States, please do not provide that information to us via our website or otherwise.
By completing a form on our website you may be consenting to receive from DMA, "commercial electronic messages" (as such term is defined in Canada's Anti-Spam Legislation (2010 S.C., ch.23 (Can.)) ("CEMs"), in such forms and containing such content as DMA may determine appropriate. You may withdraw consent to the receipt of DMA CEMs at any time by contacting DMA at unsubscribe@dmainc.com.
California Residents
In addition to the rights set forth in this policy, if you are an individual who is a California resident, you are afforded rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”). If you are a California resident and desire to exercise your rights under the CCPA, please email DMA at dmacommunications@dmainc.com.
Visitors or Residents From Outside the United States (Other Than Canada)
We only provide our services to business clients located within the United States and Canada.  Our website is not directed at and is not intended to be visited by an individual from outside the United States or Canada. No visitor to our website from outside the United States or Canada should provide any personal information to us. If you are from outside the United States or Canada, do not send any type of personal information about yourself to us or our website.
Any information you provide via our website and any technical information from the browser of your computer, tablet or mobile device will be transferred out of your country and into the United States. If you do not want any personal information to be transferred to the United States, please do not provide that information to us via our website or otherwise.
Child Protection
We understand the importance of protecting children's privacy, especially in an online environment. Our websites are not intentionally designed for or directed at children under the age of 13 years. It is our policy never to knowingly collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.
Privacy Policy Updates
This policy was last updated in March 2020. We occasionally will update our privacy policy and the terms of our website’s terms of use. Please periodically check our privacy policy and our website’s terms of use to learn of any changes thereto.  This policy supersedes all prior versions.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or comments about this policy, please submit them using the “Contact DMA” page of our website.
© 2020 DuCharme, McMillen & Associates, Inc.
All rights reserved.
